=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 8=
Xiao Maizi.
Hehe.
Mm.
You're back!
This is for you.
Where is my sister?
Why didn't she come back with you?
Your sister...
She's gone traveling the world,
hasn't she?
Yes.
Xiao Maizi.
She must've gone ahead
to see what's out there for me.
We promised
we'd see the most beautiful places
in the world together.
One day,
we will meet again.
That's right.
You will see her again.
Mm.
Xiao Maizi.
We brought you some treats.
Eat up
and grow strong.
Okay?
Xiao Maizi.
This one is good.
Is it good?
I'm going to eat well
and grow up fast.
Mm.
I promised my sister.
From now on,
I'll take care of Xiao Maizi.
I'll never marry.
I'll be there for her,
like her sister was.
I'll make sure their promise lives on.
Doctor Ge.
I have three pouches for you.
Here.
The first is a Protection Spell.
I've carved the spell into your house.
If a demon comes
or you're in danger, open it.
It will shield you from evil.
The second is a Rebirth Spell.
On the anniversary
of Xiao Maizi's sister's death,
open this pouch,
light some incense,
and it will light her way
into her next life.
Try this.
May she never know
the bitterness of this world again,
and be born into a good home.
And the third pouch...
only open it after we've left.
Remember that.
We owe you our lives. Thank you.
May you
be blessed
with good fortune,
and find smooth roads ahead,
with peace and joy all your days.
Mm.
Thank you.
Farewell. Be happy.
Hey, Yuanchu.
What did you put in that last pouch?
Why can't they open it until we leave?
All our money.
Oh.
What?
That was all our money!
In your mortal realm,
a few coins
can bring a hero to his knees.
And we've got
a whole group of Taoists here!
We're broke!
How are we supposed to get to
the Wilds of Lize?
Looks like I will have to fight dogs
for scraps again.
Money is meant to be spent.
If it buys hope for someone,
then it's money well spent.
That sounds nice and all,
but we have nothing left.
You humans can't get anywhere
without money.
Us demons have it so much easier.
Time to bring out my secret weapon.
One bite of this flatbread
keeps you full for three days,
and off the toilet for five!
The Wilds of Lize
will be a breeze with this.
Stop feeding me that nonsense!
Wow, that is amazing!
You turned it into a flying flatbread!
Why did you send everyone away
and bring me here?
Because I need you to heal me.
Our grandmaster's teachings:
Once you enter the Taoist path,
you must follow the precepts.
No lust. No attachment.
You humans always say
that a small kindness
should be repaid tenfold.
Now it's time to repay me.
I am influenced
by the Divine Stone's power.
The Purestone Bloom
holds both Yin and Yang,
so I keep shifting between forms.
If this keeps happening,
I'll wither away and die.
Only you can help stabilize my power.
But...
why me?
Enough questions.
Wake up.
You're back.
(Pesky Taoist!)
(You're going to
flatten my gorgeous face!)
Idiot.
You tricked me again.
You demons are all the same.
That's right!
I tricked you. So what?
You really have no idea
what's good for you.
Do you know how many people
dream of kissing me?
They'd give anything for the chance.
They'd cry and beg just to see me.
In the Void Realm,
thousands of souls
longed to rest on my arms.
Don't talk about yourself like that.
Oh?
You actually care about me?
Care enough
to get angry?
I...
What I care about is
whether I can fix
your Yin-Yang imbalance.
Oh.
You're not falling for me, are you?
Oh my.
That would be perfectly normal.
With charm like mine,
it's only natural.
Actually,
in my eyes,
you've always been a woman.
What?
Since when?
Ever since
you had that Deceit Beast sting me.
In my eyes,
you've been a woman all along.
The only way I can tell you've changed
is by your voice.
What?
So all this time,
you've been...
You pervert!
Keep your heart pure.
Banish demonic presence.
Let righteousness shine.
What did you just put into me?
It actually feels nice.
The Wind God Chronicle
has the power to cleanse and heal.
It should stabilize you for a while.
At least you won't suddenly
shift between genders.
From now on,
I'll heal you.
Pesky Taoist.
Trying to make me owe you even more?
To look out for one another
is what friendship is about.
But don't you humans say
there's no such thing as pure friendship
between a man and a woman?
Then a young Taoist
and a little demoness...
What would that be?
It would be...
the little demoness's...
Hey, say it again.
Say it again!
Say it again, you pesky Taoist!
Little Demoness.
Say it again.
Pesky Taoist.
Little Demoness.
Ah!
Say it! Say it! Say it!
It would be...
an old demoness.
I'll kill you!
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down;
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter the hollow fate
they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪